

Solomon Adjei

Full Stack Web Developer

I am a 28-year-old young man from Ghana who always embarks on life's journey with curiosity and an open heart. I came to Germany in June 2019 to build a career and pursue my dreams. Growing up amongst very different cultures in and outside Ghana, I developed an inner love for humanity and respect for other cultures, traditions and nationalities. I bring a globalised thinking and problem-solving mentality, which is a good tool for my tech career. I like to listen, think entrepreneurially, collaborate with others, have a good sense of humour, am very positive and would like to specialise in backend and data security.

EDUCATION

Fullstack Web Developer

DCI Digital Career Institute, Berlin

Full-time training with a focus on technologies from the MERN stack.

- Carrying out several projects, including a final full-stack project, to deepen and apply my development skills (see GitHub).
- Regularly attending weekly German classes at B2 level to continuously improve my language skills.

High School 02/2012 – 05/2015

Armed Forces (SHS), Kumasi-Ghana

SKILLS

HTML5 MongoDB CSS3 Git

JavaScript Wordpress REACT PHP

Rest API Microsoft Office

NODE JS Agile Development

Express JS Project Management

LANGUAGES

Twi (mothertongue)
English (second mothertongue)
Deutsch (B1 – B2)

KONTAKT



+49 176210-----



adjeipages1@icloud.com



Hannover

(4)

LinkedIn / Xing / GitHub

WORK EXPERIENCE

Project-Founder. November 2023– up to Date

PagesTechSolutions GmbH, Hannover

Is a TechSolution company Where I am currently part of the development team which we are working on konet2.com Plattform.

Career Persuasion Planning. 03/2022 – 08/2022

Learning German language doing some part time jobs in cleaning companies and warehouse jobs.

Working as a cleaner in a large company requires a lot of concentration, commitment and also a strong sense of humour in order to provide services for the customers and the well-being of the company.

Production worker 07/2021 – 12/2021

Miele Manufacturing Company GmbH, Lehrte German I worked in the department installing motors, cables and filters for air purification machines and other equipment, which requires high concentration and attention to avoid explosions or damage to the motors.

Migration to Germany 05

05/2019 – 06/2021

12/2022 - 12/2023

Participation in various language course and integration offers (up to B2).

Branch Manager

06/2016 - 01/2019

SafariBet Company, Kumasi Ghana

I was the manager of my branch, where I was responsible for financing and managing the affairs of the branch. After 16 months, I was able to build a strong team that made us the best in our region in terms of management and productivity.